Guide to the Dorothy Sarnoff papers, 1920-1998.
Sarnoff, Dorothy Papers, 1920-1998
- Series II. Singing Career
  - D. Programs, Billings, and Publicity Material
    - Programs/Publicity Material 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Programs/Publicity Material 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Programs/Publicity Material undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Programs/Publicity Material unrelated to Dorothy Sarnoff (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Program unrelated to Dorothy Sarnoff 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Blank Billings, handwritten list of performances (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - E. Sheet Music and Scripts
    - General Sheet Music
      - A (Box 11, Folder 1-11)
      - A-B (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - B (Box 11, Folder 13-19)
      - C (Box 11, Folder 20-31)
      - D (Box 11, Folder 32-39)
      - E (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - F (Box 12, Folder 2-8)
      - G (Box 12, Folder 9-16)
      - H (Box 12, Folder 17-21)
      - I (Box 12, Folder 22-32)
      - I-J (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - J (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
      - L (Box 13, Folder 1-10)
      - M (Box 13, Folder 11-25)
      - N (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - O (Box 13, Folder 27-29)
      - O (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - P (Box 14, Folder 2-7)
      - P-R (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - R (Box 14, Folder 9-12)
      - S (Box 14, Folder 13-21)
      - T (Box 14, Folder 22-27)
      - T (Box 15, Folder 1-10)
      - U (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
      - U-V (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - V (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - W (Box 15, Folder 16-20)
      - Y (Box 15, Folder 21-22)
      - Y-Z (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous/untitled fragments (Box 18, Folder 33-34)
      - Vocal Exercises (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Cotillion Room (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Duets (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Songs of Freedom, patriotic music compiled by Dorothy Sarnoff (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Music Catalogues (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
    - Fragile Sheet Music
      - A Paris, Francis Lemarque (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - A Sa Guitare, Francis Poulenc (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Accarezzame, Pino Calvi (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Air, Benati, A.L. Hettich (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Aria Di Adriana, Francesco Cilea (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Ariette (Dans Un Bois), Mozart (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Ave Maria, Adapted to the First Prelude of J.S. Bach, Charles Gounod (3 copies) (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Avril au Portugal (Coimbra), Raul Ferrao (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Ballatella (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Because, Edward Teschmacher, Guy D'Hardelot (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Beware of the Hawk, My Baby [Natoma], Victor Herbert (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Bind auf dein Haar, Jos Haydn (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Breit uber mein Haupt dein schwarzes Haar, Richard Strauss (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Cacilie (Cecilia), Richard Strauss (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Canto di Primavera, Pietro Cimara (2 copies) (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Ciurri, ciurri, V. U. Finni (2 copies) (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Clair de Lune, Claude Debussy (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Cradle Song, Brahms (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Csardas [The Bat/Die Fledermaus], Johann Strauss (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Danny Boy, Old Irish Air, Fred E. Weatherly (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - De l'autre cote de la rue, Michel Emer (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Der Bescheidene Schafer, Joseph Marx (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Dicitencello Vuie, Enzo Fusco, Rodolfo Falvo (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Dors mon Enfant, Richard Wagner (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Duett Und Szene [Rosalinda] (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - E Se Un Giorno Tornasse, Ottorino Respighi, Vittoria Aganoor-Pompilj (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Ernani, G. Verdi (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Es blaut die Nacht [Julius Caesar], Georg Friedrich Handel (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Evening Fair, Achille Claude Debussy, Paul Bourget (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Fantoches, Claude Debussy, Paul Verlaine (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Femmes, battez vos Marys, Traditional song, arr. Arnold Bax (2 copies) (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Gia Il Sole Dal Gange, A. Scarlatti (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Green, Achille Claude Debussy, Paul Verlaine (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Guitares Et Mandolines, C.Saint-Saens (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Heimkehr Vom Feste, Leo Blech (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - How could I fain have slumber'd [Der Freishutz], C.M. v. Weber (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - I Want to Sing in Opera [The Siren], Worton David, George Arthurs, Jerome Kern (2 copies) (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Ich Liebe Dich, Edvard Grieg (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - If Guiltless Blood Be Your Intent, George Frideric Handel (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Il Barbiere Di Siviglia, G. Rossini (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Il Est Doux, Il Est Bon [Herodiade], J. Massenet (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - It Might As Well Be Spring [State Fair], Rodgers & Hammerstein II (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - La Boheme: Mimi's Farewell (Addio Di Mimi) (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - La Boheme: Mimi's Song (Si mi chiamano Mimi) (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - La Boheme: Musetta's Valse Song (Quando me'n vo soletta) 2 copies (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - La Boheme: Musetta's Valse Song (Quando me'n vo soletta), 2 copies (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - La Canzone Di Doretta, Giuseppe Adami (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - La Damoiselle Elue, Claude Debussy, D.G. Rossetti (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - La Danza, G. Rossini (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - La Goualante du Pauvre Jean, Marguerite Monnot, Rene Rouzaud (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - La Partida (The Farewell), F. M. Alvarez (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - La Prise De Troie, H. Berlioz (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - La Seine, Guy LaFarge, Flavien Monod (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - La Wally, Alfredo Catalani (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - La Wally, Alfredo Catalani (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - L'Ame Des Poetes, Charles Trenet (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Laughter and Tears, Franz Schubert, Friedrich Ruckert, Frederick H. Martens (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Le Temps des Lilas, Maurice Bouchor, Ernest Chausson (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Les Feuilles Mortes, Jacques Prevert, Joseph Kosma (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Les Noces de Figaro, Mozart (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - L'Hiver, Charles Koechlin (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Love and Music, These Have I Lived For [Tosca], G. Puccini, W. Beatty-Kingston (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Love's Philosphy, Roger Quilter, Shelley (2 copies) (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Ma Poupee cherie, D. de Severac (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - M'Ama... Non M'Ama, P. Mascagni (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Marechiare, F. Paolo Tosti, S. Di Giacomo (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Merce, dilette amiche, Giuseppe Verdi (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Miranda, Hilaire Belloc (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Molly Malone (Cockles and Mussels), Traditional (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Munasteria 'e Santa Chiara, Alberto Barberis, Michele Galdieri (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - My Lover is a Fisherman, Lily Strickland (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - 'Na Voce, 'Na Chitarra E 'O Poco 'E Luna, Ugo Calise, C.A. Rossi (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Nina, G.B. Pergolesi (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Nocturne, Ernest Chausson, Maurice Bouchor (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - None But the Lonely Heart, Piotr Il'ych Tchaikovsky (2 copies) (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Novembre, Edouard Tremisot, Paul Bourget (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - O del mio amato ben,S. Donaudy (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - O del mio dolce ardor, C.W. von Gluck (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - O Dolce Concento, W.A. Mozart (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Obeissons quand leur voix, Jules Massenet, Willis Wager (2 copies) (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Oh Dear! What can the matter be?, Arnold Pax (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - One Night Of Love, Gus Kahn, Victor Schertzinger (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Orpheus With His Lute, Sir Arthur Sullivan (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Ouvre ton Coeur [Carmen], Georges Bizet, Louis Delatre (3 copies) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Over the Steppe, A. Gretchaninoff, A. Pleschtscheyeff (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Padam...Padam..., Henri Contet, Norbert Glanzberg (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Parlami D'amore Mariu!, Ennio Neri, C. A. Bixio (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Piece En Forme De Habanera, Maurice Ravel (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Pres des remparts de Seville [Carmen], Georges Bizet, H. Meilhac, L. Halevy, F. W. Rosier (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Quattro Liriche, Ottorino Respighi (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Racconto Di Maddalena [Andrea Chenier], U. Giordano (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Recit et Air de Lia [L'Enfant Prodigue], E. Guinand (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Regrets de Manon [Manon], J. Massenet (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Rimpianto, Enrico Toselli (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Romance De L'Etoile, Emmanuel Chabrier, E. Leterrier, A. Vanloo (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Romanza Di Adriana, Francesco Cilea (3 copies) (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Scena, Aria E Miserere [Il Trovatore], Giuseppe Verdi (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Schlichte Weisen, Richard Strauss (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Serenatella sciue-sciue, Ettore De Mura, Ferdinando Albano (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - She never told her love, Franz J. Haydn (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Sie Wissen's Nicht, Richard Strauss (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Song of the Open, Frank La Forge (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Sonnez Les Matines, J. Charles Rousseliere (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sorrow, Sorrow, Stay, Leo Sowerby, John Dowland (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Speak to Me of Love, Bruce Siever, Jean Lenoir (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Spiando Ai Vetri, Pietro Cimara, Carlo Zangarini (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Standchen, Richard Strauss (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Stornellatrice, C. Zangarini, A. Donini, Ottorino Respighi (3 copies) (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Tarentelle, Georges Bizet (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - The Buckle, Walter De La Mare (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - The Fairy Tree, Vincent O'Brien (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - The Lover's Pledge, Richard Strauss (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - The Mouse-Trap, Hugo Wolf (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - The Old Maid's Song, Howard Brockway (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - The Sweetest Story Ever Told, R. M. Stults (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - The Time for Making Songs Has Come, James H. Rogers (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - The Tryst, Jean Sibelius (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Tilimbom, Igor Strawinsky (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - To You, Richard Strauss (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Toujours, Gabriel Faure, Charles Grandmougin (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Tu Me Plais, Jacques Dutailly (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Un Bel Di (One Fine Day) [Madame Butterfly], G. Puccini (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Un Jour, Tu Verras [Secrets D'Alcove], Mouloudji, Georges van Parys (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Va godendo vezzoso e bello (Trip, blithe streamlet, merrily dancing), G. F. Handel, Albert G. Latham, W. Gillies Whittaker (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Vergebliches Standchen (The Vain Suit), Johannes Brahms (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - Vieille Chanson Espagnole, Louis Aubert, Arsene Houssaye (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Voi lo Sapete (Surely you know), Mascagni (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - Were my song with wings provided (Si mes vers avaient des ailes!), Reynaldo Hahn, Victor Hugo, Th. Baker (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - When I Bring to You Colour'd Toys, John Alden Carpenter, Rabindranath Tagore (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - When Love is Kind, Thomas Moore (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - Who Can I Turn To (When Nobody Needs Me), Leslie Bricusse, Anthony Newley (3 copies) (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - You Do Something To Me [Night and Day], Cole Porter (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Oversized Sheet Music
      - A Christmas Carol, Arnold Bax (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - All of You, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - All the Way (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Bleuet, Arnold Bax (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Blue Danube [Great Waltz] (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Dance Everyone Dance, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Dance, Everyone, Dance, Sid Danoff (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Domino, Louis Ferrari, Jacques Plante, Ray Wright (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Domino, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Four Songs to Death, Paul Creston, Rabindranath Tagore (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Gott im Fruhling, Franz Schubert (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - I Wish You Love, Charles Trenet, Albert A. Beach (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - I'm in Love with Vienna, Johann Strauss Sr. & Jr., Oscar Hammerstein II (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Italian Medley (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - It's Deductable, Negative stats (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - I've Been Too Busy [Mr. Wonderful] (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - I've Grown Accustomed to Her Face [My Fair Lady], Frederick Loewe, Alan Jay Lerner (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Kiss of Fire (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - La Danza, G. Rossini (2 copies) (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Life Is A Beautiful Thing, Arr. Carl Hoff (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Love Medley, Arr. Peter Matz (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Lover (Opening Routine) (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Medley, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Most Unusual Day, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - My Laddie, W.A. Thayer, Princess Troubetzkoy (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - My Man, Arr. Eddie Safranski (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Piano Number (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Psalm XXIII, Paul Creston (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Return from the Banquet, Leo Blech, Marcel Frank (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Scarlet Ribbons (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Seguidille, Jacques Dupont, Th. Gautier (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Serse, G.F. Handel (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Take My Love [The Glass Slipper], Helen Deutsch, Bronislau Kaper (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - The Ballade of the Sea-Side Maiden (written for Dorothy Sarnoff), Adeline Oppenheimer, Marilyn Shapiro (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - The Bird of the Wilderness, Paul Creston, Rabindranath Tagore (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - The King and I, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - The World Has Its Eyes on You, Denes Agay, Bob Osborne, George Herz (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Today I Love Everybody, Arr. Ernie Bragg (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Un Bel Di, negative stats (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - When I Come Home Again, Denes Agay, Bob Osbourne, George Herz (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous extra pages (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Music by Heitor Villa-Lobos
      - Bachianas Brasileiras No. 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Chansons Typiques Bresiliennes (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Magdalena- Festival of the River (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- Food For Thought (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- Lost (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- The Emerald (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- The Forbidden Orchid (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- The Omen Bird (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Magdalena- The Seed Of God (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Cancao do Marinheiro (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Lundu da Marqueza de Santos (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Cantilena (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - A Gatinha Parda (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Remeiro de S. Francisco (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Nhapope (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Modinhas e Cancoes - Evocacao (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Voila la vie (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Inutile epigramme (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Songe d'une nuit d'ete (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Epigremme (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Perversite (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Pudeur (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Image (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Partition d'Orchestra, Epigrammes ironiques et sentimentales: Poesie de Ronald de Carvalho - Verite (Comme l'opera lyrique) (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Cancao Do Carreiro (Cancao De Um Crepusculo Caricioso) (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Chromo (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Desejo (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Passaro Fugitivo (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Sonho (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Viola (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Vocal Music
      - A (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - A-F (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - F (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - F-H (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - H (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
      - H-R (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - R-S (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - T (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - T-Z (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Jewish Music Catalogues (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Fiddler on the Roof (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Milk and Honey (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The King and I
      - Anna and Son Klin (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Getting to Know You (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Hello, Young Lovers (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
      - I Have Dreamed (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Now You Leave (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Shall We Dance (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
      - Something Wonderful (Box 18, Folder 17-21)
      - Medley (Box 18, Folder 22-31)
      - Script (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Song Books
      - 40 (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
      - 50 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
      - 93 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - A (Box 16, Folder 26-33)
      - B (Box 16, Folder 34-36)
      - C (Box 16, Folder 37-46)
      - D (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - D (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - E (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
      - F (Box 17, Folder 5-9)
      - G (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
      - I (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
      - J (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - L (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
      - M (Box 17, Folder 18-20)
      - O (Box 17, Folder 21-23)
      - P (Box 17, Folder 24-27)
      - R (Box 17, Folder 28-30)
      - S (Box 17, Folder 31-36)
      - T (Box 17, Folder 37-39)
      - T (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - U (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - V (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
      - W (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
      - Miscellaneous/Untitled (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Fragile Songbooks
      - Acht Liedchen (Eight Songs), Leo Blech (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Ariettes Oubliees (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Canciones Clasicas Espanolas, F.J. Obradors (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Ciganske Melodie (Gypsi Songs), Anton Dvorak (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Edith Piaf, Henri Contet (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Folk-Songs, Chanteys and Singing Games, Charles H. Farnsworth, Cecil J. Sharp (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Funf Kleine Lieder, Richard Strauss (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Lieder Album, Richard Strauss (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Masters of Russian Song, Edited by Kurt Schindler (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Melodies, Henri Duparc (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - French Canadian Songs, G.A. Grant-Schaefer (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Franz Schubert Songs with Pianoforte Accompaniment, Vol I. (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Pathways of Song: Volume III High Voice, Frank La Forge, Will Earhart (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Raccolta di Canzoni Celebri, Ernesto Tagliaferri (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Songs of Scotland, Compiled and Arranged by J. Bodewalt Lampe (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Songs with Pianoforte Accompaniment Edward MacDowell (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Tambien Castilla Canta: Coleccion de 10 Canciones Castellanas (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - The Merry Widow, Franz Lehar (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Vingt Chants Populaires Espagnols: Deuxieme Cahier, Joaquin Nin (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Scripts
      - Die Fledermaus,(fragments) (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Impromptu (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Rosalinda (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
      - The Great Waltz (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
      - The New Moon (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - The Vagabond King (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Magdalena (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - F. Recordings
    - 8mm film of My Darlin Aida, 1952 (Box 3)
    - Audio Recording labeled Dorothy and Wingate, Nov 14, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Box of 4 Audio Recordings labeled Jim Toliver (Box 3)
    - Charlie Is My Darling/Think On Me, Michelle O'Duffy Show (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Unmarked (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Let Me Be Like the Girl on the Prowl/One Kiss, Chicago Theater of Air, May 22, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - I'll Follow My Secret Heart/ Medley-Apple Blossoms, CBS, June 6, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Tell Me That You Love Me / Sweethearts, May 20, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ciribiribin/The Jewel Song (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ciribiribin/The Jewel Song (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Lover, Treasury Guest Star, Jan 22, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Lover, Treasury Guest Star, Jan 22, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Legeres Hirondelles, Metropolitan Auditions of the Air, Feb 2, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sweet Songs Of Long Ago/ The Song Is You, WOR Recording, Sept 25, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - The Grey Kitten/When Love Is Kind, WOR Recording, Sept 18, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Unmarked (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Unmarked (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Herodiade/Psyche, Treasury Concert, June 20, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Some Day, Full Speed Ahead Program, Oct 15, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - My Hero, Full Speed Ahead Program, Nov 10, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Variety - Alfred Drake, WABC, Nov 19, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Labiamo, James Melton Program, Feb 9, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Through the Years, WNYC, Mar 5, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Don De Latiere, WNYC, Mar 5, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Scout About Town, part 2, WOR, Aug 5, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Scout About Town, part 3, WOR, Aug 5, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - What's Your Opinion, parts 1&4, WOR (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - What's Your Opinion, parts 2&5, WOR (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - What's Your Opinion, parts 6&3, WOR (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Tacea la Notte Placida - Il Trovatore, Nov 9, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Tacea la Notte Placida - Il Trovatore, Nov 9, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - When I Have Sung My Songs, Jan 21, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Aria from Il Trovatore, Jan 28, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Make Believe - Show Boat/ How Strange, Aug 22, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Pagliacci, Nov 15, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pagliacci, Nov 15, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - D'amor sull'ali - Il Trovatore (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Nuit d'amour - Tales of Hoffman; Songs My Mother Taught Me - Dvorak, Metropolitan Auditions of the Air Finalist (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Last Rose of Summer, May 2, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Last Rose of Summer, WABC Great Moments in Music, Sept 9, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - D. S. and the Ray Bloch Orchestra, Feb 19, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Interview - Martha Deane(broken), Jan 11, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Interview - Martha Deane(broken), Jan 11, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Excerpt - Hugette Waltz, June 10, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Excerpt - Voi Lo Sapete, June 10, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Concert, sides 1&3, WQXR, June 20, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Treasury Concert Psyche(broken), WQXR, June 20, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The Friendly Beasts / O Holy Night, WNBC, Dec 21, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Father of Mercy / Something Wonderful, Woolworth Hour, Jan 8, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff and Robert Rounseville on Jane Pickens Show, May 5, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Jane Pickens Show, May 12, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Jane Pickens Show with Dorothy Sarnoff, May 19, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff on Jane Pickens Show, May 26, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Dorothy Sarnoff Singing, WRCA, June 2, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 50)